let questions = [
{
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who was the first Formula 1 driver to win 7 world championships?",
    answer: "Michael Schumacher",
    options: [
        "Lewis Hamilton",
        "Alain Prost",
        "Michael Schumacher",
        "Fernando Alonso"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 2,
    question: "What year did England last win the World Cup?",
    answer: "1966",
    options: [
        "1966",
        "1970",
        "1962",
        "1964"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 3,
    question: "How many gold medals did Team GB win at the 2012 Olympics?",
    answer: "29",
    options: [
        "25",
        "27",
        "28",
        "29"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who was the longest reigning manager of Manchester United Football Club?",
    answer: "Alex Ferguson",
    options: [
        "Eric Ten Hag",
        "David Moyes",
        "Alex Ferguson",
        "Jose Mourinho"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 5,
    question: "Who was the first woman to win the Wimbledon Singles Championship?",
    answer: "Maud Watson",
    options: [
        "Lena Rice",
        "Serena WIlliams",
        "Maud Watson",
        "Shirley Fry"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 6,
    question: "How many Premier League titles has Pep Guardiola won as a manager?",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
        "5",
        "7",
        "9",
        "11"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 7,
    question: "How many sports are broadcasted during the Olympics?",
    answer: "40",
    options: [
        "40",
        "38",
        "42",
        "36"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 8,
    question: "Who won the Moto GP tournament in 2020?",
    answer: "Joan Mir",
    options: [
        "Johann Zarco",
        "Joan Mir",
        "Alex Rins",
        "Valentino Rossi"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following teams has won the most NFL Superbowl's?",
    answer: "New England Patriots",
    options: [
        "Miami Dolphins",
        "Dallas Cowboys",
        "Green Bay Packers",
        "New England Patriots"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who has won the most Ballon d'Or awards?",
    answer: "Lionel Messi",
    options: [
        "Christiano Ronaldo",
        "Lionel Messi",
        "Johan Cruyff",
        "Rivaldo"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 11,
    question: "Who was the runner up to the 2008 Formula 1 World Championship?",
    answer: "Felipe Massa",
    options: [
        "Lewis Hamilton",
        "Kimi Raikkonen",
        "Felipe Massa",
        "Sebastian Vettel"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 12,
    question: "The largest transfer in football history was Â£198 million. Who was the player?",
    answer: "Neymar",
    options: [
        "Neymar",
        "Kylian Mbappe",
        "Christiano Ronaldo",
        "Garteh Bale"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 13,
    question: "Which team is the most successful in NASCAR History?",
    answer: "Hendrick Motorsports",
    options: [
        "Hendrick Motorsports",
        "Team Penske",
        "Petty Enterprises",
        "Joe Gibbs Racing"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 14,
    question: "How many PGA Golf Tour events has Tiger Woods won?",
    answer: "82",
    options: [
        "46",
        "53",
        "82",
        "71"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 15,
    question: "How many NBA basket ball championships did Michael Jordan win?",
    answer: "6",
    options: [
        "7",
        "6",
        "5",
        "4"
    ]
}
]